Guide to the Jazz Loft Project Records, 1950-2012 and undated RL.10001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Research Notes, Articles, and Materials
  This series contains documentation of research undertaken by Sam Stephenson, Dan Partridge, and other Jazz Loft Project assistants, and includes articles, images, notes, printouts of various resources from the internet, and ephemera. Subjects researched include the life and work of jazz musicians related to the Jazz Loft; many facets of New York City history including architecture, crime statistics, music and musicians, artists and artistic spaces, the Flower District, the West Village, and prostitution; and individuals directly related to the Jazz Loft building, including Dick Cary, Thelonious Monk, Hall Overton, and David X. Young.
  - Paper files
    - Ansel Adams, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Agee, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Toshiko Akiyoshi, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Calvin Albert, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Mose Allison, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Michael Almereyda, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Frank Amoss, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Roberta Arnold, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - David Amram, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - TJ Anderson (Composer), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Chuck Andrus, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Ron Anthony, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Diane Arbus, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Larry Austin, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Edgar Bateman, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Avakian Brothers, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Astrologer Ellen Bach, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Jeanne Baer, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Lars Bagge, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - David Parker, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Danny Barker/Banjo Party, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Whitney Balliet, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Lucy (Guerlac) Battersby, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Ronnie Bedford, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - John Berg, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Warren Bernhardt, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Eddie Burt, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Hal Bigler, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Loran Blacklock, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Carla Bley, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Paul Bley, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Dupree Bolton, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - (Richard) Dick Borden, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Eduourd Boubet, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Stan Brakage, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Dollar Brand-Abdullah Ibrahim, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Buzz Brunner, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Henry Cartier-Bresson, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Bob Brookmeyer, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - John Benson Brooks, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Roy Brooks, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Dan Budnick, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Vinnie Burk, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Nico Bunick, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Maude Callen, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - James Caplinger-Kansas Smith Cousins, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Hamilton Carson, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Dick Cary, 2006-2009 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Dolph Castellano, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Talib Rasul Hakim AKA Stephen Alexander Chambers, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Teddy Charles, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Don Chastain, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Sonny Clark, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Joe Cocuzzo, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Gil Coggins, RIP, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - John Cohen, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Al Cohn, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Ornette Coleman, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Columby, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Alice Coltrane, undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Clarence Cooper, Jr., 2006 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Arlene "Corwin", 2009 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Eddie Costa, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Clyde Cox, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Bill Crow, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Ronnie Cuber, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Bob and Jenne Cunningham, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Mike Cuozzo, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Salvador Dali Happening, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Salvador Dali, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Sonny Dallas, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Phil Dante, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Ted D'Arms, undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Dennis Russell Davies, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Bob Decelle, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Peter Maxwell Davies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Charles Davis, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Charles Deforest, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Jacob Deschin, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Norman Diamond, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Dottie Dodgion, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Eric Dolphy, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Bob Dorough, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Lou Draper, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Frank Driggs, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Eddie Duran, undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Manny Duran, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Bob Dylan, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Martin Eagle, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Jon Eardley, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Norman Edge, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Bruce Eisenbeil, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Bob Elliot, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Don Ellis, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - James Enyeart, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Bill Evans, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Gil Evans, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Medgar Evers, undated (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Dick Cary Diaries-1954 [Restricted], undated (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Dick Cary Diaries-1954 [Restricted], undated (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Dick Cary Diaries-1955-1959 [Restricted], undated (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Dick Cary Diaries-1955-1959 [Restricted], undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Dick Cary Diaries-1955-1959 [Restricted], undated (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Dick Cary Diaries-1955-1959 [Restricted], undated (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Joseph McGuire, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Jack Reilly, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Tenderloin Playbill, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Frederick Franck, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Basil Rathbone "Julius Caeser" Playbill, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Chasing the Rising Sun/Ted Anthony, undated (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Magnum/Saga of Eugene Smith, undated (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Heroin Panic-1960's, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Herbert Huncke Reader, undated (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Jane Getz Manuscript, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Jane Getz Manuscript, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - Will Faller, undated (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Harold Feinstein, ca. 1988 (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - Ruth Fetske, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Marissa Flores, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 119)
    - Marty Forscher, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 120)
    - Charley Fox, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 121)
    - Ronnie Free, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Robert Frank, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Art Freed, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Dave Frishberg, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Tony Fruscella, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Curtis Fuller, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Paul Fusco, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Helen Gee/Limelight, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Jane Getz, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Dan Gioia/NEA Jazz, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Jimmy Giuffre, 1998-2005 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Dorrie Glenn, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Eddie Gomez, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Cyra Greene, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Stanley Greene, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Freddie Greenwell, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Bob Greger, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Dick Griffin, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Henry Grimes, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Sid Grossman, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Gigi Gryce, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Wayne Gutierrez, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Ahmed Abdul-Malik, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Manhattan Percussion Ensemble, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Wingy Malone, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Lucas Mason, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Joe Masters, 2004-2007 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Earl May, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Grace Mayer, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Dave McKenna, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Ray/Chris McKenna, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - McPartland, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Robert B. Menschel, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Don Menza, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Darius Milhaud, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Wayne Miller, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Gjon Mili, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Charles Mingus, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Gretchen Monahan, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Thelonious Monk, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Thelonious Monk, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Robert "Gorilla" Monsoon, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Carman Moore, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Charles Moore, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Marty Morell, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - John Morris, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Sal Mosca, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Jim & Jane Hall, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Lin Halliday, 2003-2006 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Yvonne & Phillipe Halsman, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Leonid Hambro, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Wendell Harrison, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Ilka Hartman, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Ralph Hattersley, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Gary Hawkins, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Roy Haynes, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Dave Heath, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Michael Heffernan, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Bill Heine, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Frank Hewitt, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Ken Heyman, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Ed Hubble, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Roy Haynes, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Fons Ianelli, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Peter Ind, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Dollar Brand/Abdullah Ibrahim, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Chuck Israels, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Ira Jackson, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Al Jeter, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Thomas "Tomas" Johns/Janda, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Lester Johnson, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - William Johnson/CCP, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Jim Karales, 2000-2005 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Dick Katz, 2000-2006 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Robin D. G. Kelley, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Jack Kerouac, undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Roland Kirk, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Lincoln Kirstein (on Smith), undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Jimmy Knepper, undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Elie Nadelman, Eugene Smith, Lincoln Kirstein, Cartier-Bresson, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Race Newton, undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Nehama Hendel, 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Long John Nebel, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - LJN-Donald Bain, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Al Neese, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Mike Nock, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Walter Norris, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Hod O'Brien, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Joe "King" Oliver, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Smith Oliver, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - George Orick, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Robert "Bob" Ornstein, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - George T. Orrick, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Nancy Overton, 2002-2007 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Rick Overton, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Ray Parker, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Art Pepper, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Skip Parsons, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Shorty Pederstein, undated (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Simon Harvey Perkhoff, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Dana Perna, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Sandy Perpetua, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Barre Phillips, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Ed Phyfe, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Bill Pierce, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Paul Plummer, 2003-2006 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Bill Potts, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Thomas Pynchon (Monk), 2006 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - James "The Amazing" Randi, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Jimmy Raney, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Steve Reich, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Jack Reilly, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Freddie Redd, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Myra Resnik, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Ben Riley, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Shorty Rogers, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Sonny Rollins, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Sam Rosenberg, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - David Rothman, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Brian Rosenkrantz, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Pete Rose, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Charlie Rouse, undated (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Roswell Rudd, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Vinnie Ruggiero, 2003-2007 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Ted Runge, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Pee Wee Russell, undated (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Charles Russo, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Aaron Sachs, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Kumi Sato, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Steve Sbarge, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - George Schiffer, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Lalo Schifrin, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Alexander Sasha Schneider, undated (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Gunther Schuller, undated (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Pete Seeger, undated (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Peter Serkin, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Clarence Sharpe, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Burt Shavitz, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Jean Shepherd, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Larry Shustak, 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Dave Sibley, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Pete "Carola" Sims, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Zoot Sims, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Alvin Singleton, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Aileen Mioko Smith, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Mark Snow, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - Jeremy Steig, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - James I. "Jimmy" Stevenson, 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Jean Swain, undated (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Tabnik, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Art Taylor, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - John Tchicai, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Carole Thomas, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Willie Thomas, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Al Thompson, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 155)
    - Dave Tofani, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - Charles Tolliver, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - Walter Trampler, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Ludmila Ulehla, undated (Box 2, Folder 159)
    - Turk Van Lake, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - David Vestal, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - David Vestal, ca. 2005 (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - Frank Vicari, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 163)
    - Roman Vishniak, undated (Box 2, Folder 164)
    - Mitchell Vlachos, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 165)
    - J. Robert Wagoner, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 166)
    - Virginia Abbot-Wald & Ted Wald, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 167)
    - Butch Warren, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 168)
    - Butch Warren, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - Dudley Watson, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 170)
    - Freddie Watts, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 171)
    - Patty Waters, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Dan Weaks, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Dan Weiner NYC, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Tommy Wayburn, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Barney Wilen, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Howard Williams, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Howard Williams, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - John A. Williams, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - John Windhurst, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - John Wilson, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Phil Woods, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Phil Woods, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Jim Wormworth, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Paul Worthington, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Pete Yellin, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Arthur Zitrin, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - David X. Young/Eliza Young, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - David X. Young, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Albert Esformes, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Francis X. O'Connor, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - F. Livingston Pell, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Pilgrim Holding Company, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Quackenbos, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - James and John Slater, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Isaac Varian, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Harry N. Weasel, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Republican Club/11th District, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - U.S. Trust CD, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Committee for Fourteen, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Committee 14/15, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Organized Crime--20th Century, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Max Aaron, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - George Aronoff, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - George Bliss, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Henry Clark, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Andrew Coleman, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - John F. Delaplaine, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Edwin A. Ely, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Charles J. Hardy, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - George Hencken, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - David Jaffe, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - A. E. Lister, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Various Bibliographies, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Manhattan Gang History, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Greek Communiy/Flower Ind., 2006 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Directory to Seraglios/Gentleman's Companion, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Commercialized Prostitution in NYC, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Fast Man's Directory & Lover's Guide, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - City of Eros & Index, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Gotham--Leads & References, undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - CDS Research Project, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Flower District, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - NYC History Articles & Bib., 2004-2006 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Arcadia, undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - NYC-Blizzards, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Democracy Committee--11th Assembly District, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Hellenic Furnishing Company (473 Sixth Ave), undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Joy Garden--Street History, undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - JFK-Oswald, undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Knickerbocker Cottage, undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Martin's Club, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Rainbow Restaurant, undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - John Sloan, undated (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Street Culture-Automat, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Staten Island, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - 1929 Subway Bombing, undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Tin Pan Alley, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Willoughby's Camera & Camera Row News, undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - JLP Neighborhood Articles & Pix, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Behind the Green Lights/Cornelius W. Willemse, undated (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Loft Neighborhoods Odd #s/102 W. 29th, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Jack Reilly, undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Loft Neighbors-Even #s, undated (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Loft Tape Article References, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Steppin' Out--NYC Nightlife, undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - NY Streetscapes-Loft Area, undated (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Gambling & Prostitution-Tenderloin Culture, undated (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Eugene Smith Loft Artifacts, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Random Smith Files/Articles, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Smith Slide Copies/Scans, undated (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Sonia Katchian Loft Photo, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Smith Materials, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Smith Materials, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Smith Press, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - FOIA, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Lamp Unto My Feet Film Inventory, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Ron Free/Smith as Sivana, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Kevin Smith, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Smith/Drugs/Klein, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Smith Workshos, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Smith in Japan, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Photo League, ca. 2005 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Obtaining Military Records, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Smith Minimata & Misc, 2004-2007 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Hall Oveton Articles, ca. 2005 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Harvey Overton, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Thelonious Monk Scores, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Hall Overton Scores, 1961-1964 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Hall Overton Scores, 1961-1964 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Hall Overton Bios and Reviews, 1971-2004 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Overton Articles and Monk Scores, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Hall Overton Research, 2003-2006 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Hall Overton Research, 2003-2006 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Hall Overton Research, 2003-2006 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Overton Military Info, 2004-2007 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Overton-Monk Articles and Transcripts, 2006-2009 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Bangor: A History in Photographs, 2004-2006 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Smith/Orick Letters from CCP, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Smith Letters Archive/CCP, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Smith Letters Archive/CCP, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - W. Eugene Smith Letters/CCP, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - W. Eugene Smith Letters/CCP, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Darius Milhaud (Overton Teacher), 2007 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Sixth Avenue Articles, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Deeds for 826 Building, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Loft & Neighborhood History, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Post CCP Visit Research, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Chelsea Photo/Leases (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - NYC-Midtown Images-Misc, ca. 2004 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Street History-NYC Hotels, ca. 2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Loft Documents--Entire List, ca. 2004 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Thomas O'Brien, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Kid Miller, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - James Varnum, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Russell Stebbins--Dry Dock Bank, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - James W. Ripley, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - David Sherman, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Charles Peabody, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - F. Livingston Pell, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Emil Paul-Silver Grill, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Building Records, ca. 2006 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - NYC-Dept. Bldgs-821 6th Ave, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - 6th Avenue Elevated Train, 2004-2006 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - 5th Avenue History-14 -> Madison Sq. Parallel to Loft Track, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Assorted Articles and Research, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - 1954-1959 Loft Neighborhood Phonebooks, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Directory/Seraglios & Gentleman's Companion, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - UFOs, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Loft Neighborhood Other Blocks, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - NYC Dept. Buildings, 2003-2006 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - 821 Sixth Ave./473 Sixth Ave., ca. 2006 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Loft Neighborhood Timeline/Articles, ca. 2004-2006 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Jazz & Race Articles, 1987-2001 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Jazz & Race Articles, 2003-2008 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Gambling Articles, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Drug Articles, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Drug History Articles, ca. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - "The Connection" Play, 2005-2007 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Georges Avril, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Sofia Coppola, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Stan Brakage, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - ESP Records, ca. 2010 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Barry Farber-Radio Opposite Long John Nebel, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Charles Ives, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Elia Kazan, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Robin D. G. Kelley, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Sydney Lumet, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Harry Lunn--CIA/Art Pealer, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Branford Marsalis, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Mr. Mudd, ca. 2003 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Walter Murch, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Eugene O'Neill, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Fred Roos, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Ned Rorem, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Salgado, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Tony Schwartz-Sound Recorder, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - George Bernard Shaw, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Jean Shepherd, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Dr. Nathan Kline, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 51)